export const kanjiList_origin =
{
    0: [],
    1: [
        {
            "id": 2101,
            "question": "瑰麗",
            "answer": "かいれい",
            "level": 1,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-20 03:02:47"
        },
        {
            "id": 2102,
            "question": "烏鵲",
            "answer": "うじゃく",
            "level": 1,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-20 03:02:47"
        },
        {
            "id": 2103,
            "question": "解傭",
            "answer": "かいよう",
            "level": 1,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-20 03:02:47"
        },
        {
            "id": 2104,
            "question": "安佚",
            "answer": "あんいつ",
            "level": 1,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-20 03:02:47"
        },
        {
            "id": 2105,
            "question": "胡乱",
            "answer": "うろん",
            "level": 1,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-20 03:02:47"
        },
        {
            "id": 2106,
            "question": "邏卒",
            "answer": "らそつ",
            "level": 1,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-20 03:02:47"
        },
        {
            "id": 2107,
            "question": "闃然",
            "answer": "げきぜん",
            "level": 1,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-20 03:02:47"
        },
        {
            "id": 2108,
            "question": "間隙",
            "answer": "かんげき",
            "level": 1,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-20 03:02:47"
        },
        {
            "id": 2109,
            "question": "千仞",
            "answer": "せんじん",
            "level": 1,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-20 03:02:47"
        },
        {
            "id": 2110,
            "question": "蒐集",
            "answer": "しゅうしゅう",
            "level": 1,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-20 03:02:47"
        },
        {
            "id": 2111,
            "question": "咫尺",
            "answer": "しせき",
            "level": 1,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-20 03:02:47"
        },
        {
            "id": 2112,
            "question": "稼穡",
            "answer": "かしょく",
            "level": 1,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-20 03:02:47"
        },
        {
            "id": 2113,
            "question": "刈穫",
            "answer": "がいかく",
            "level": 1,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-20 03:02:47"
        },
        {
            "id": 2114,
            "question": "浅葱",
            "answer": "あさぎ",
            "level": 1,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-20 03:02:47"
        },
        {
            "id": 2115,
            "question": "仇讐",
            "answer": "きゅうしゅう",
            "level": 1,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-20 03:02:47"
        },
        {
            "id": 2116,
            "question": "煢然",
            "answer": "けいぜん",
            "level": 1,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-20 03:02:47"
        },
        {
            "id": 2117,
            "question": "飛礫",
            "answer": "つぶて",
            "level": 1,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-20 03:02:47"
        },
        {
            "id": 2118,
            "question": "関雎",
            "answer": "かんしょ",
            "level": 1,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-20 03:02:47"
        },
        {
            "id": 2119,
            "question": "顧眄",
            "answer": "こべん",
            "level": 1,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-20 03:02:47"
        },
        {
            "id": 2120,
            "question": "臚列",
            "answer": "ろれつ",
            "level": 1,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-20 03:02:47"
        }],
    2: [
        {
            "id": 1601,
            "question": "酪農",
            "answer": "らくのう",
            "level": 2,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:12:27"
        },
        {
            "id": 1602,
            "question": "彙報",
            "answer": "いほう",
            "level": 2,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:12:27"
        },
        {
            "id": 1603,
            "question": "刹那",
            "answer": "せつな",
            "level": 2,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:12:27"
        },
        {
            "id": 1604,
            "question": "甚大",
            "answer": "じんだい",
            "level": 2,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:12:27"
        },
        {
            "id": 1605,
            "question": "憤り",
            "answer": "いきどおり",
            "level": 2,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:12:27"
        },
        {
            "id": 1606,
            "question": "溺愛",
            "answer": "できあい",
            "level": 2,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:12:27"
        },
        {
            "id": 1607,
            "question": "頻発",
            "answer": "ひんぱつ",
            "level": 2,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:12:27"
        },
        {
            "id": 1608,
            "question": "尚早",
            "answer": "しょうそう",
            "level": 2,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:12:27"
        },
        {
            "id": 1609,
            "question": "肯定",
            "answer": "こうてい",
            "level": 2,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:12:27"
        },
        {
            "id": 1610,
            "question": "雪渓",
            "answer": "せっけい",
            "level": 2,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:12:27"
        },
        {
            "id": 1611,
            "question": "嫡子",
            "answer": "ちゃくし",
            "level": 2,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:12:27"
        },
        {
            "id": 1612,
            "question": "臆面",
            "answer": "おくめん",
            "level": 2,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:12:27"
        },
        {
            "id": 1613,
            "question": "霜害",
            "answer": "そうがい",
            "level": 2,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:12:27"
        },
        {
            "id": 1614,
            "question": "一蹴",
            "answer": "いっしゅう",
            "level": 2,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:12:27"
        },
        {
            "id": 1615,
            "question": "土壌",
            "answer": "どじょう",
            "level": 2,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:12:27"
        },
        {
            "id": 1616,
            "question": "旋回",
            "answer": "せんかい",
            "level": 2,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:12:27"
        },
        {
            "id": 1617,
            "question": "醜悪",
            "answer": "しゅうあく",
            "level": 2,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:12:27"
        },
        {
            "id": 1618,
            "question": "露呈",
            "answer": "ろてい",
            "level": 2,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:12:27"
        },
        {
            "id": 1619,
            "question": "顕著",
            "answer": "けんちょ",
            "level": 2,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:12:27"
        },
        {
            "id": 1620,
            "question": "国璽",
            "answer": "こくじ",
            "level": 2,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:12:27"
        }
    ],
    3: [
        {
            "id": 1001,
            "question": "欧米",
            "answer": "おうべい",
            "level": 3,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:11:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 1002,
            "question": "遂行",
            "answer": "すいこう",
            "level": 3,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:11:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 1003,
            "question": "郊外",
            "answer": "こうがい",
            "level": 3,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:11:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 1004,
            "question": "促進",
            "answer": "そくしん",
            "level": 3,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:11:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 1005,
            "question": "鍛錬",
            "answer": "たんれん",
            "level": 3,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:11:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 1006,
            "question": "放浪",
            "answer": "ほうろう",
            "level": 3,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:11:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 1007,
            "question": "犠牲",
            "answer": "ぎせい",
            "level": 3,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:11:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 1008,
            "question": "移籍",
            "answer": "いせき",
            "level": 3,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:11:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 1009,
            "question": "古墳",
            "answer": "こふん",
            "level": 3,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:11:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 1010,
            "question": "衰退",
            "answer": "すいたい",
            "level": 3,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:11:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 1011,
            "question": "花壇",
            "answer": "かだん",
            "level": 3,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:11:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 1012,
            "question": "模倣",
            "answer": "もほう",
            "level": 3,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:11:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 1013,
            "question": "請願",
            "answer": "せいがん",
            "level": 3,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:11:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 1014,
            "question": "阻害",
            "answer": "そがい",
            "level": 3,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:11:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 1015,
            "question": "逮捕",
            "answer": "たいほ",
            "level": 3,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:11:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 1016,
            "question": "窒息",
            "answer": "ちっそく",
            "level": 3,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:11:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 1017,
            "question": "塗料",
            "answer": "とりょう",
            "level": 3,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:11:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 1018,
            "question": "陶芸",
            "answer": "とうげい",
            "level": 3,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:11:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 1019,
            "question": "殺伐",
            "answer": "さつばつ",
            "level": 3,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:11:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 1020,
            "question": "排斥",
            "answer": "はいせき",
            "level": 3,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:11:24"
        }
    ],
    4: [
        {
            "id": 401,
            "question": "介護",
            "answer": "かいご",
            "level": 4,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:10:16"
        },
        {
            "id": 402,
            "question": "派遣",
            "answer": "はけん",
            "level": 4,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:10:16"
        },
        {
            "id": 403,
            "question": "兼務",
            "answer": "けんむ",
            "level": 4,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:10:16"
        },
        {
            "id": 404,
            "question": "処分",
            "answer": "しょぶん",
            "level": 4,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:10:16"
        },
        {
            "id": 405,
            "question": "互角",
            "answer": "ごかく",
            "level": 4,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:10:16"
        },
        {
            "id": 406,
            "question": "逃避",
            "answer": "とうひ",
            "level": 4,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:10:16"
        },
        {
            "id": 407,
            "question": "沖",
            "answer": "おき",
            "level": 4,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:10:16"
        },
        {
            "id": 408,
            "question": "欄干",
            "answer": "らんかん",
            "level": 4,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:10:16"
        },
        {
            "id": 409,
            "question": "天賦",
            "answer": "てんぷ",
            "level": 4,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:10:16"
        },
        {
            "id": 410,
            "question": "木陰",
            "answer": "こかげ",
            "level": 4,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:10:16"
        },
        {
            "id": 411,
            "question": "専攻",
            "answer": "せんこう",
            "level": 4,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:10:16"
        },
        {
            "id": 412,
            "question": "依然",
            "answer": "いぜん",
            "level": 4,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:10:16"
        },
        {
            "id": 413,
            "question": "偉容",
            "answer": "いよう",
            "level": 4,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:10:16"
        },
        {
            "id": 414,
            "question": "鈍感",
            "answer": "どんかん",
            "level": 4,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:10:16"
        },
        {
            "id": 415,
            "question": "監視",
            "answer": "かんし",
            "level": 4,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:10:16"
        },
        {
            "id": 416,
            "question": "闘志",
            "answer": "とうし",
            "level": 4,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:10:16"
        },
        {
            "id": 417,
            "question": "投影",
            "answer": "とうえい",
            "level": 4,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:10:16"
        },
        {
            "id": 418,
            "question": "荒天",
            "answer": "こうてん",
            "level": 4,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:10:16"
        },
        {
            "id": 419,
            "question": "小豆",
            "answer": "あずき",
            "level": 4,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:10:16"
        },
        {
            "id": 420,
            "question": "歳入",
            "answer": "さいにゅう",
            "level": 4,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-18 09:10:16"
        }
    ],
    5: [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "株式",
            "answer": "かぶしき",
            "level": 5,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-17 14:46:09"
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "発揮",
            "answer": "はっき",
            "level": 5,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-17 14:46:09"
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "縦断",
            "answer": "じゅうだん",
            "level": 5,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-17 14:46:09"
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "創造",
            "answer": "そうぞう",
            "level": 5,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-17 14:46:09"
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "question": "著者",
            "answer": "ちょしゃ",
            "level": 5,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-17 14:46:09"
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "question": "郵便",
            "answer": "ゆうびん",
            "level": 5,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-17 14:46:09"
        },
        {
            "id": 7,
            "question": "宇宙",
            "answer": "うちゅう",
            "level": 5,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-17 14:46:09"
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "question": "射的",
            "answer": "しゃてき",
            "level": 5,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-17 14:46:09"
        },
        {
            "id": 9,
            "question": "胸筋",
            "answer": "きょうきん",
            "level": 5,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-17 14:46:09"
        },
        {
            "id": 10,
            "question": "宣言",
            "answer": "せんげん",
            "level": 5,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-17 14:46:09"
        },
        {
            "id": 11,
            "question": "専門",
            "answer": "せんもん",
            "level": 5,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-17 14:46:09"
        },
        {
            "id": 12,
            "question": "机上",
            "answer": "きじょう",
            "level": 5,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-17 14:46:09"
        },
        {
            "id": 13,
            "question": "空論",
            "answer": "くうろん",
            "level": 5,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-17 14:46:09"
        },
        {
            "id": 14,
            "question": "吸飲",
            "answer": "きゅういん",
            "level": 5,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-17 14:46:09"
        },
        {
            "id": 15,
            "question": "賃貸",
            "answer": "ちんたい",
            "level": 5,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-17 14:46:09"
        },
        {
            "id": 16,
            "question": "糖分",
            "answer": "とうぶん",
            "level": 5,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-17 14:46:09"
        },
        {
            "id": 17,
            "question": "窓口",
            "answer": "まどぐち",
            "level": 5,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-17 14:46:09"
        },
        {
            "id": 18,
            "question": "額面",
            "answer": "がくめん",
            "level": 5,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-17 14:46:09"
        },
        {
            "id": 19,
            "question": "俳優",
            "answer": "はいゆう",
            "level": 5,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-17 14:46:09"
        },
        {
            "id": 20,
            "question": "宝刀",
            "answer": "ほうとう",
            "level": 5,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "TypingOh",
            "updated_at": "2022-10-17 14:46:09"
        }
    ],
    6: [
        {
            "id": 3001,
            "question": "圧力",
            "answer": "あつりょく",
            "level": 6,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "typingoh",
            "updated_at": "2023-11-26 17:58:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 3002,
            "question": "利益",
            "answer": "りえき",
            "level": 6,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "typingoh",
            "updated_at": "2023-11-26 17:58:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 3003,
            "question": "液体",
            "answer": "えきたい",
            "level": 6,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "typingoh",
            "updated_at": "2023-11-26 17:58:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 3004,
            "question": "格別",
            "answer": "かくべつ",
            "level": 6,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "typingoh",
            "updated_at": "2023-11-26 17:58:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 3005,
            "question": "寄る",
            "answer": "よる",
            "level": 6,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "typingoh",
            "updated_at": "2023-11-26 17:58:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 3006,
            "question": "金額",
            "answer": "きんがく",
            "level": 6,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "typingoh",
            "updated_at": "2023-11-26 17:58:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 3007,
            "question": "過度",
            "answer": "かど",
            "level": 6,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "typingoh",
            "updated_at": "2023-11-26 17:58:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 3008,
            "question": "用件",
            "answer": "ようけん",
            "level": 6,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "typingoh",
            "updated_at": "2023-11-26 17:58:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 3009,
            "question": "飼育",
            "answer": "しいく",
            "level": 6,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "typingoh",
            "updated_at": "2023-11-26 17:58:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 3010,
            "question": "意識",
            "answer": "いしき",
            "level": 6,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "typingoh",
            "updated_at": "2023-11-26 17:58:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 3011,
            "question": "査定",
            "answer": "さてい",
            "level": 6,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "typingoh",
            "updated_at": "2023-11-26 17:58:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 3012,
            "question": "謝礼",
            "answer": "しゃれい",
            "level": 6,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "typingoh",
            "updated_at": "2023-11-26 17:58:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 3013,
            "question": "表示",
            "answer": "ひょうじ",
            "level": 6,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "typingoh",
            "updated_at": "2023-11-26 17:58:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 3014,
            "question": "規定",
            "answer": "きてい",
            "level": 6,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "typingoh",
            "updated_at": "2023-11-26 17:58:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 3015,
            "question": "勢力",
            "answer": "せいりょく",
            "level": 6,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "typingoh",
            "updated_at": "2023-11-26 17:58:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 3016,
            "question": "酒税",
            "answer": "しゅぜい",
            "level": 6,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "typingoh",
            "updated_at": "2023-11-26 17:58:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 3017,
            "question": "常温",
            "answer": "じょうおん",
            "level": 6,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "typingoh",
            "updated_at": "2023-11-26 17:58:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 3018,
            "question": "備える",
            "answer": "そなえる",
            "level": 6,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "typingoh",
            "updated_at": "2023-11-26 17:58:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 3019,
            "question": "賛同",
            "answer": "さんどう",
            "level": 6,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "typingoh",
            "updated_at": "2023-11-26 17:58:24"
        },
        {
            "id": 3020,
            "question": "採取",
            "answer": "さいしゅ",
            "level": 6,
            "ver": 1,
            "del_flg": 0,
            "updated_by": "typingoh",
            "updated_at": "2023-11-26 17:58:24"
        }
           ]
}